<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Key's Corner!</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Key's Corner!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:57:33 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keyaedisa.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>newKai + newKaiso</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/newkai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:57:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/newkai/</guid><description>newKai is the successor to a project I called Kairo. Kairo was my first attempt at building my own Arch ISO. Kairo used Arco&amp;rsquo;s base. newKai was created because I quickly realized Kairo was not truly a custom Arch ISO. Since it used a lot of Arco&amp;rsquo;s stuff it was really just a custom Arco ISO. newKai was created to remedy this.
As development on newKai moved forward a few core ideals were realized.</description></item><item><title>ValenOS</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/valenos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:57:23 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/valenos/</guid><description>ValenOS is the successor to newKai. After all the time I spent working on newKai, I realized it had become kind of unique to my Macbook&amp;rsquo;s hardware. ValenOS was created to bring the fixes I made for my Macbook&amp;rsquo;s family of network cards to other Macbook&amp;rsquo;s, but also make it installable on different hardware.
There are some differences between newKai but ultimately I realized I was just fine with using Xero and so now it serves as a private project I can test things on.</description></item><item><title>ValenSE</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/valense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 17:57:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/valense/</guid><description>ValenSE is the ISO I built for my server. I have a server I use and maintain for data storage purposes as well hosting my own website and potentially minecraft server.
It taught me alot about how to setup Linux and a bootloader for a BIOS non-UEFI system. It is a command line only OS and comes bundled only with what&amp;rsquo;s needed to boot live and install. It&amp;rsquo;s meant to be an Arch based OS that is just right for those who need a server OS and nothing more.</description></item><item><title>Beginning of my blog!</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/beginningofblog/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:00:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/beginningofblog/</guid><description>Welcome to my blog! Hello all! I&amp;rsquo;m Keyaedisa or Key for short! I am 22 years old and nonbinary. My pronouns are they/them. I am a developer who is also getting into the cyber security space. I plan on opening up my own security firm someday and getting into the iOS security space. I am passionate about nearly all things technology and love learning more. I have been learning a lot about programming and linux this past year.</description></item><item><title>abs 3.0</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/abs3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:22:16 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/abs3/</guid><description>abs 3.0 is another rewrite of abs. It adds several options over 2.0. abs 3.0&amp;rsquo;s presence in the terminal is also different than that of 2.0. It has been redesigned to be simpler yet still retaining the color and liveliness of abs 2.0. Output has been streamlined and it is overall a big improvement over 2.0.
The project repo can be found at abs github!
One of the biggest features now available in abs 3.</description></item><item><title>abs 2.0!</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/abs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 19:54:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/projects/abs/</guid><description>Intro The most recent compiled version of abs is hosted on my package repo called Valen and can be found at Valen Repo!
The project repo can be found at abs github!
abs is a terminal utility I wrote in bash meant to not only automate the build process of any archiso profile it is provided, but to also make it an interative process. It allows you to customize the contents of your profiledef.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 18:10:12 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid><description>Hi! My name&amp;rsquo;s key and this is my first test post! I am not sure what to put here but this is just a test!</description></item></channel></rss>