<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Key's Corner!</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Key's Corner!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 19:28:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ssh Tips and Tricks</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/ssh-t-and-t/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 19:28:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/ssh-t-and-t/</guid><description>SSH Tips and Tricks! Hi! I was inspired to make a post about SSH that could be used as a somewhat quick reference for some basic SSH commands and tips and tricks regarding proper usage practices. Below you will find summaries of a few articles I found to have useful information. This way I felt would be better both for me writing this blog quickly and also for allowing you the reader to quickly read and decide what reference you actually need.</description></item><item><title>Ssh Tips and Tricks</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/ssh-tips-and-tricks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 19:28:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/ssh-tips-and-tricks/</guid><description>SSH Tips and Tricks! Hi! I was inspired to make a post about SSH that could be used as a somewhat quick reference for some basic SSH commands and tips and tricks regarding proper usage practices. Below you will find summaries of a few articles I found to have useful information. This way I felt would be better both for me writing this blog quickly and also for allowing you the reader to quickly read and decide what reference you actually need.</description></item><item><title>Feb23</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/feb23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 17:40:56 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/feb23/</guid><description>Feb Update Adding vnanorc to projects as well as valuca. Updated age in about me.</description></item><item><title>Project Updates!</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/intro-abu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 16:17:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/intro-abu/</guid><description>Welcome Hi all. In this post I will be updating you all on what I am currently working on. See below:
abu abu is an in development terminual utility written in C and bash. It starts an ncurses TUI that makes the archiso creation process newbie friendly. abs will be deprecated on abu&amp;rsquo;s first release.
Project goals
multiple user profiles that can be passed to custom add/delete/modify user profiles attractive tui thats easy to use ValenSE Yes I am picking ValenSE up again.</description></item><item><title>About Key</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/aboutme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:58:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/aboutme/</guid><description>Hello! My name is Keyaedisa! You can call me Key for short. I am a 22 year old developer and junior security researcher. I am nonbinary and my pronouns are they/them. I am self taught and really enjoy the challenge of teaching my self what it takes. I am apart of the team at XeroLinux and responsible for the program known as abs used to build the Xero and XeroG ISO&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Beginning of my blog!</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/beginningofblog/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 21:00:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/beginningofblog/</guid><description>Welcome to my blog! Hello all! I&amp;rsquo;m Keyaedisa or Key for short! I am 22 years old and nonbinary. My pronouns are they/them. I am a developer who is also getting into the cyber security space. I plan on opening up my own security firm someday and getting into the iOS security space. I am passionate about nearly all things technology and love learning more. I have been learning a lot about programming and linux this past year.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 18:10:12 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://keyaedisa.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid><description>Hi! My name&amp;rsquo;s key and this is my first test post! I am not sure what to put here but this is just a test!</description></item></channel></rss>